https://cherrysind.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Home
/
Privacy Policy | Cherry's IndustrialCherry’s Industrial is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to Cherry’s Industrial ‘s websites and governs data collection and usage. Collection of your Personal InformationCherry’s Industrial collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home and/or work address and/or telephone number. Cherry’s Industrial also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Cherry’s Industrial. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.In the event that you contact us for customer support through the website, we may also request that you provide additional User Information relevant to the support requested by you. Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide customer support in the event that relevant information related to the use of our products or services is withheld. We may retain communications relating to customer support, and/or information drawn from such communications, for statistical and/or reference purposes.Use of your Personal InformationCherry’s Industrial collects and uses your personal information to operate Cherry’s Industrial websites and deliver the services you have requested. Cherry’s Industrial may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Cherry’s Industrial and its affiliates Cherry’s Industrial may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services. Cherry’s Industrial does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Cherry’s Industrial may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Cherry’s Industrial may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Cherry’s Industrial, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. Cherry’s Industrial does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. Cherry’s Industrial keeps track of the websites and pages you visit within Cherry’s Industrial, in order to determine what products and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising on our websites to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Cherry’s Industrial’s websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served Cherry’s Industrial’s or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Cherry’s Industrial’s (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Cherry’s Industrial’s, or the public.If you provide Cherry’s Industrial’s with user information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:To review the user information that you have supplied to usTo request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to usTo request that your user information not be used to contact youTo request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we useTo request that your user information be deleted from our records andTo opt out of being solicited by this website or third partiesIf you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third partySecurity of your Personal InformationNo method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. Cherry’s Industrial’s uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Cherry’s Industrial’s secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementCherry’s Industrial’s will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback Cherry’s Industrial’s encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Cherry’s Industrial’s is protecting your information.Enforcement of this Privacy StatementIf you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us at info@cherrysind.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or we have not addressed your inquiry to your satisfaction, you should then contact us at abuse@cherrysind.comContact InformationCherry’s Industrial welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Cherry’s Industrial has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Cherry’s Industrial at 877-350-2729. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.Need Help? contact us
Request a brochure
Sign up forour newsletter
Apply forFinancing
CHERRY’S NEWSLETTER
Subscribe
×
Call Us Today! 800-350-0011Email Us!Request more info600 Morse Ave. Elk Grove Village, IL 60007Monday - Friday, 8:00 AM - 5:00 PMSocialAbout Cherry'sAbout UsContact UsOur StaffNewsletterHow Do I Get A Quote?Resource CenterIndustrial InsiderVideoBlog SitemapMy AccountRegister/LoginMy WishlistMy Account    Terms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicySitemap
Copyright © 2020 |
Cherry's Industrial Equipment Corp
Back to Top
